Steven Ferreira

Sugar Hill, GA • 6786348820 • ferreira206@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Confident and highly organized individual with more than 7 years working as a Service Advisor in the automotive industry. Experienced in ADP/ CDK and Reynolds & Reynolds. Knowledgeable of multiple vehicle manufacturers including Toyota, Nissan, and FCA. Capable of multi-tasking and ready for new and exciting challenges.

Skills

- Account management
- Technical support
- Client rapport
- Staff education and training

- Reporting and documentation
- Complaint resolution
- Knowledgeable in ADP and Reynolds & Reynolds
- Route dispatch

Work History

Service Advisor, 10/2019 to Current

Rick Hendrick Chrysler Dodge Jeep Ram of Duluth - Duluth, GA

- Pleasantly greeted customers and asked open-ended questions to better determine needs
- Suggested add-on services that would be helpful to customers and improve bottom line
- Handled customer issues with confidence, using pproficient customer service to provide effective resolution
- Researched complex problems and resolved issues using automotive knowledge and industry experience

Service Advisor. 08/2013 to 10/2019

Autonation Toyota Scion Mall Of Georgia - Buford, GA

- Suggested add-on services that would be helpful to customers and improve bottom line
- Researched complex problems and resolved issues using automotive knowledge and industry experience
- Pleasantly greeted customers and asked open-ended questions to better determine needs
- Handled customer issues with confidence, using proficient customer service to provide effective resolution

Service Advisor, 09/2017 to 01/2019

Beaver Toyota of Cumming - Cumming, GA

- Handled customer issues with confidence, using proficient customer service to provide effective resolution
- Capitalized on multiple upsell opportunities with new and potential customers, resulting in 40% increase in revenues
- Pleasantly greeted customers and asked open-ended questions to better determine needs
- Suggested add-on services that would be helpful to customers and improve bottom line

Education

Bachelor of Applied Science in Information Technology: Management Information Systems, Expected in 05/2021

Georgia Institute of Technology - Atlanta, GA